<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My City</string>
    <string name="kavkaz_title">Café Yagam</string>
    <string name="kavkaz_description">A cozy café offering a mix of Filipino and Western dishes, perfect for casual dining. It’s known for its locally sourced ingredients and offers a relaxing ambiance.</string>
    <string name="kavkaz_address">Address: 2nd Floor, SM City Tarlac, McArthur Highway, San Roque, Tarlac City</string>
    <string name="genacvale_title">The Magsaysay Restaurant</string>
    <string name="genacvale_description">Located along Magsaysay Avenue, this restaurant serves a range of Filipino favorites with a focus on fresh, local ingredients. It’s a great place for family gatherings or casual meals.</string>
    <string name="genacvale_address">Magsaysay Avenue, Tarlac City, Tarlac</string>
    <string name="black_angus_title">Tarlac Café</string>
    <string name="black_angus_description">A popular spot for traditional Filipino breakfast and other local dishes. The restaurant is known for its comfort food and homey feel.</string>
    <string name="black_angus_address">Rizal St., Poblacion, Tarlac City, Tarlac</string>
    <string name="sakurada_title">Max’s Restaurant</string>
    <string name="sakurada_description">Known for its fried chicken and Filipino comfort food, Max’s is a staple in the Philippines and has a branch in Tarlac City for a familiar taste of home-style meals. </string>
    <string name="sakurada_address"> McArthur Highway, San Roque, Tarlac City, Tarlac</string>
    <string name="beer_academy_title">The Tasting Room</string>
    <string name="beer_academy_description">Known for its relaxed ambiance and variety of drinks, this bar offers a great spot for those looking for a quiet but stylish place to enjoy a drink.</string>
    <string name="beer_academy_address">2nd Floor, Tarlac Leisure Park, Brgy. San Sebastian, Tarlac City</string>
    <string name="dargett_title">The Pub at Tarlac</string>
    <string name="dargett_description">A well-loved pub with karaoke nights, sports events, and a great range of alcoholic beverages.</string>
    <string name="dargett_address">McArthur Highway, San Roque, Tarlac City, Tarlac</string>
    <string name="lovers_park_title">Tarlac Recreational Park</string>
    <string name="lovers_park_description">This park offers a peaceful environment with walking trails, picnic areas, and open spaces, making it a great place for family outings and relaxation.</string>
    <string name="lovers_park_address">Brgy. San Rafael, Tarlac City, Tarlac</string>
    <string name="victory_park_title">Capas National Shrine</string>
    <string name="victory_park_description">This historical site is also a park that honors the Filipino and American soldiers who died during World War II. It has peaceful grounds and walking paths, ideal for those interested in history and nature.</string>
    <string name="victory_park_address">Capas, Tarlac</string>
    <string name="miniso_title">SM City Tarlac</string>
    <string name="miniso_description">A major shopping mall in the city, SM City Tarlac offers a wide range of retail stores, dining options, entertainment, and services. It’s home to various brands, from fashion to electronics, and also features a supermarket, department store, and cinemas.</string>
    <string name="miniso_address">McArthur Highway, San Roque, Tarlac City, Tarlac</string>
    <string name="tsiran_title">Puregold Tarlac</string>
    <string name="tsiran_description">A well-known retail chain, Puregold Tarlac offers groceries, household products, and affordable consumer goods. It also has a selection of other retail outlets within the mall.</string>
    <string name="tsiran_address">McArthur Highway, San Roque, Tarlac City, Tarlac</string>
    <string name="rio_mall_title">Uniqlo Tarlac</string>
    <string name="rio_mall_description">Known for its casual wear, Uniqlo offers a variety of clothing for men, women, and children, focusing on comfort and simplicity.</string>
    <string name="rio_mall_address">SM City Tarlac, McArthur Highway, San Roque, Tarlac City, Tarlac</string>
    <string name="vernissage_title">Tarlac Eco-Tourism Park</string>
    <string name="vernissage_description">A nature park that features walking trails, wildlife, and serene landscapes, ideal for nature lovers and those looking to experience the outdoors in a peaceful environment.</string>
    <string name="vernissage_address">Brgy. San Vicente, Tarlac City</string>
    <string name="cascade_title">Aquino Center and Museum</string>
    <string name="cascade_description">The Aquino Center and Museum commemorates the legacy of the Aquino family, particularly former President Corazon Aquino and her late husband, Benigno Aquino Jr.  </string>
    <string name="cascade_address">Capas, Tarlac</string>
    <string name="northern_avenue_title">Monasterio de Tarlac</string>
    <string name="northern_avenue_description">A religious and spiritual destination, Monasterio de Tarlac is a serene sanctuary located atop a hill. The monastery is home to a large statue of the Divine Mercy and offers stunning views of the surrounding countryside. It’s a peaceful place for meditation, reflection, and scenic views.</string>
    <string name="northern_avenue_address">San Jose, Tarlac</string>
    <string name="metro_title">Mount Pinatubo</string>
    <string name="metro_description">While not directly within the city, Mount Pinatubo is a popular attraction located in the nearby town of Capas. Visitors can hike to the crater lake of this active volcano and enjoy a scenic view of the turquoise waters surrounded by rugged terrain. The trek is a thrilling adventure for outdoor enthusiasts.</string>
    <string name="metro_address">Capas, Tarlac</string>
    <string name="restaurants_category">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="bars_category">Bars</string>
    <string name="parks_category">Parks</string>
    <string name="shops_category">Shops</string>
    <string name="attractions_category">Other Attractions</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="next_button">Next</string>
    <string name="previous_button">Previous</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="yerevan_title">Tarlac City</string>
    <string name="yerevan_description">Tarlac City, the capital of Tarlac Province in Central Luzon, Philippines, is an important economic, cultural, and historical hub. Known for its agricultural significance, the city produces rice, sugarcane, and other crops. It is home to historical landmarks like the Capas National Shrine and plays a role in the Philippine Revolution. The city has experienced rapid urbanization with modern infrastructure and commercial developments. Tarlac City offers a blend of urban and rural landscapes, rich culture, and easy access to other parts of Luzon.</string>
</resources>